# JUAN FRANCISCO ROBLES ARIAS

PROJECT LEADER | FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

(52) 81 1010 5529

ifcorobles@outlook.com

Monterrey, Nuevo León, México.

# **ABOUT ME**

I am a project leader with experience in project management and software development, utilizing tools like Jira and agile methodologies such as Scrum and Kanban. As a full stack developer with expertise in .NET, Angular, and SQL Server, I have designed and maintained ERP functionalities and resolved bugs. I have successfully managed the release of SAT (Tax Administration Service) requirements and possess in-depth knowledge of ERP administration

# **SKILLS**

- AngularJS / Angular
- Javascript Typescript
- .NET Framework
- ASP.Net
- SQL Server
- GIT

- NodeJS
- Azure
- HTML
- CSS
- PostgresSQL
- Jira
- Slack

# **EXPERIENCE**

## 2021 - 2024 | PROJECT LEADER - FULL STACK DEVELOPER | BIND ERP

As a Project Leader, I planned and coordinated the delivery of updates and requirements, ensuring adherence to deadlines and project scope. I led multifunctional teams, managed risks, and resolved issues to maintain alignment with objectives and meet stakeholder expectations.

## 2018 - 2021 | FULL STACK DEVELOPER | BIND ERP

As a developer, I focused on creating new functionalities for the system, as well as performing maintenance and making necessary corrections.

## 2016 - 2018 | FULL STACK DEVELOPER | UANL CDIS

I was responsible for developing and releasing various custom projects for the industry. As a software factory, I worked on projects of all kinds, including inventory, logistics, appointment scheduling, banking, etc.

## **EDUCATION**

## 2021 - 2022 | MASTER OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION - MBA, DIGITAL MARKETING

Universidad Tecmilenio

2020 - 2021 | MASTER OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION - MBA, PROCESS QUALITY AND PRODUCTIVITY Universidad Tecmilenio

2019 - 2020 | MASTER OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION - MBA, FINANCES

Universidad Tecmilenio

2010 - 2015 | BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Universidad Autónoma de Nuevo León

## **REFERENCES**

### **ALEJANDRO BONILLA**

Bind ERP Founder (52) 81 1588 1157

## **ROLANDO VALDEMAR**

Full-Stack Developer (52) 81 3416 0385

### MIGUEL CONTRERAS

Full-Stack Developer (52) 81 1906 0186

## **ERNESTO HERNANDEZ**

Full-Stack Developer (52) 81 1763 4432